# **Pepe Doval**

Cell: +34-650-795-886 Email: pepellou@gmail.com

I am a senior software developer with 10+ years of experience, seeking for new places to develop my craft. I'm an advocate for Agile Methodologies and Software Craftsmanship, as well as a very active member of the Spanish Agile community. Despite my leadership skills, my passion is coding.



#### Education

## **University of Vigo**

Major: Computer Science Engineering

Minor: Physics

Predoctoral studies: Artificial Intelligence

**Courses:** Pedagogical skills, bioinformatics, graphic design, free software, web frameworks, ...

Skills

## Software sculpting skills

Unit testing, pair programming, agile methodologies, full stack.

#### Personal skills

Ethics, team leadership, professionalism, value oriented.

#### Experience

#### Trabeculae E.B.T.

Head of IT/Developer - Ourense, Spain - 2008-2010

- Developed software for building three-dimensional models from bone microtomography
- · Designed and developed core internal software for the company
- Developed a software for medical follow-up of patients after hip surgery

## **Agil-AZ**

CEO/Developer - Santiago de Compostela - 2010-2014

- Run the company from scratch. Managed to hire a small team of developers :-)
- Developed 40+ software projects, mostly for startups
- Mostly web development; also mobile apps and backend
- Explored and perfected the use of different methodologies: Scrum, Kanban, XP, etc.

## **Hermanos Karapatrov**

Software Sculptor - Milladoiro - 2011-2013

- Contributed to 10+ audiovisual projects
- Mostly real time image processing; also some web development and graphic design
- Kanban

# **SetPay**

Full Stack Developer - Santiago de Compostela - 2014-2017

- Contributed to development of front-end and back-end of the core products
- Trained other developers
- · Methodology leader
- · Mostly bank software, Java technologies and Angular
- Scrum

# NoLegalTech

The Tech Guy - Fully remote - 2018-today

- To the eyes of our customers, I do magic to create what they want from their ideas
- I also extinguish tech fires
- Mostly web development (full stack)
- Kanban

#### **Hobbies**

Chess, Maths, Books

Hackathons and Coding Dojos

#### Languages

Native: Galician, Spanish

Fluent: English

Studied: French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Russian